olioboard.com 2018-11-23

# Privacy Policy | Olioboard

Olioboard (www.olioboard.com) is a Keele UX product. At Keele UX Inc, we respect the privacy of our users and the importance of the information they entrust to us. With this in mind, we provide you this privacy policy (the “Policy”) to help you understand the kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit the Site or use any of our Services, how we may use and disclose the information, and how you can control, correct and/or update the information. By visiting the Olioboard website or using the Olioboard services, you are accepting the policies and practices described in this Policy. Each time you visit the Olioboard website or use the Olioboard services, you agree and expressly consent to our collection, use and disclosure of the information that you provide as described in this Policy.

### THE OLIOBOARD.COM PRIVACY POLICY WAS LAST UPDATED ON: DECEMBER 13 2011.

We may collect information that can identify you (“personal information”), such as your name and email address when you provide it to us when using our website or in some other manner.

We also may collect other types of information in the following ways when you visit our Olioboard website:

  * Our server logs automatically collect information, such as your IP address, your browser type and language, and the date and time of your visit, which helps us track users’ movements around our site and understand trends.
  * We may use standard Internet tools, such web beacons, which collect information that tracks your use of our website and enables us to customize our services and advertisements.

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. Should we ever do so, we will comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act.

We may use information to:

  * Fulfill your requests for products and services;
  * Process payment for products or services you order via our website;
  * Facilitate use of our website;
  * Manage your account and your preferences;
  * Analyze use of and improve our website, products and services;
  * Identify and protect against fraudulent transactions and other misuses of our website;
and 
  * Enforce our Terms of Use.

We will not share your personal information with others except as indicated below, or except when we inform you in advance and give you the opportunity to opt out. We may share personal information with:

  * Service providers, such as credit-card payment processors, performing services on our behalf;

You may choose:

  * Not to provide personal information, although that may result in your inability to obtain certain services or use certain features of our website;
  * To stop receiving promotional emails or newsletters from us by sending an email to the contact address at the bottom of this policy;
  * To delete or decline cookies by changing your browser settings, although if you do so, some of the features or services of our website may not function properly;
  * To review and update your personal information by contacting us at the email address below or, if you have an online account on our website, by logging into that account.

We take appropriate commercially reasonable physical, electronic, and other security measures to help safeguard personal information from unauthorized access, alteration, or disclosure.

The Olioboard website may link to websites operated by third parties that we do not control. We do not monitor, control, or endorse the information collection or privacy practices of any third parties. We strongly encourage you to become familiar with the privacy practices of every website you visit and to contact them if you have any questions about their respective privacy policies and practices. This Policy applies solely to information collected by us through the Olioboard website or services and does not apply to these third-party websites. The ability to access information of third parties from the Olioboard website or services, or links to other websites or locations, is for your convenience only and does not signify our endorsement of such third parties, their products, services, websites, locations, or their content.

Olioboard reserves the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Policy at any time and without prior notice, and any changes will become effective immediately upon being posted unless we advise you otherwise. However, we will not use your Personal Information in a way that is materially different than the uses described in this Policy without giving you an opportunity to opt out of such differing uses. Your continued use of the Olioboard website or services after this Policy has been amended shall be deemed to be your continued acceptance of the terms and conditions of the Policy, as amended. We encourage you to bookmark this Web page and review this Policy regularly.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or your dealings with the Olioboard website, you can contact us at info@olioboard.com or get in touch by mail:  
Privacy Matters  
c/o Keele UX Inc.  
5412 Cambie St.  
Vancouver, BC  
V5Z 3A1  

©2011 Keele UX, Inc.. All rights reserved.

Linked information:

**Cookies:**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record keeping purposes. Cookies can be either session cookies or persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when you close your browser and is used to make it easier for you to navigate our website. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time.  
For example, when you sign in to our website, we will record your user or member ID and the name on your user or member account in the cookie file on your computer. We also may record your password in this cookie file, if you indicated that you would like your password saved for automatic sign-in. For security purposes, we will encrypt any usernames, passwords, and other user or member account-related data that we store in such cookies. In the case of sites and services that do not use a user or member ID, the cookie will contain a unique identifier. We may allow our authorized service providers to serve cookies from our website to allow them to assist us in various activities, such as doing analysis and research on the effectiveness of our site, content and advertising. 

You may delete or decline cookies by changing your browser settings. (Click "Help" in the toolbar of most browsers for instructions.) If you do so, some of the features and services of our website may not function properly.

We may allow third-parties, including IAC companies, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements on our site. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. Our website does not provide any personal information to these third parties, but they may collect information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw and/or clicked on the advertisements they deliver, and possibly associate this information with your subsequent visits to the advertised websites. They also may combine this information with personal information they collect from you. The collection and use of that information is subject to the third-party’s privacy policy. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness. Some of these third-party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies (www.networkadvertising.org).

**Web Beacons:**  
Web beacons (also known as clear gifs, pixel tags or web bugs) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users or to access cookies. Unlike cookies which are stored on the user’s computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on the web pages (or in email) and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence.  
Web beacons may be used to deliver or communicate with cookies, to count users who have visited certain pages and to understand usage patterns. We also may receive an anonymous identification number if you come to our site from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website. 

Close

Create 2D & 3D rooms that you can save, shop2 & share.

Close

Create 2D & 3D rooms that you can save, shop1 & share.

## 1\. Your Acceptance

Olioboard and its subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively "Olioboard.com") provides service to you subject to the following Terms of Use, which may be updated by us from time to time without notice to you. These Terms of Use constitute a binding agreement between Olioboard.com and you governing your use of the Website. By using and/or visiting the www.olioboard.com Website or any other Websites owned by Olioboard.com (collectively the "Website"), you signify your assent to both these Terms of Use and the Olioboard.com Privacy Policy, which is specifically incorporated into the Olioboard.com Terms of Use. You are only authorized only to use the Website if you agree to abide by all applicable laws and to these Terms of Use. Please read these Terms of Use carefully. If you do not agree to these Terms of Use, please do not use the Website.

## 2\. Website Access

Olioboard.com hereby grants you permission to use the Website as set forth in these Terms of Use, provided that: (i) your use of the Website as permitted is solely for your personal, noncommercial use; (ii) you will not copy or distribute any part of the Website in any medium without Olioboard.com’s prior written authorization; (iii) you will not alter or modify any part of the Website other than as may be reasonably necessary to use the Website for its intended purpose; and (iv) you will otherwise comply with the terms and conditions of these Terms of Use.

In order to access some features of the Website, you will have to create an account. You are not allowed to use another user’s account without permission. When creating your account, you must provide accurate and complete information. You are solely responsible for the activity that occurs on your account, and you must keep your account password secure. You may change your password at any time by updating your Account Profile page. In addition, you agree to immediately notify Olioboard.com of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security. Olioboard.com cannot and will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with this Section 2.

By registering with Olioboard.com, you represent that you are of legal age to form a binding contract and are not a person barred by any laws from using the Olioboard.com Website. You agree to provide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself in all required fields of the registration form. If any of your information changes, you agree to update your registration information as soon as possible. If Olioboard.com suspects that your registration information is not complete, current, or accurate, or that you have otherwise violated these Terms of Use, your account may be subject to suspension or termination, and you may be barred from using the Olioboard.com Website.

You agree not to use or launch any automated system, including without limitation, "robots," "spiders," or similar technological devices or programs, that access the Website in a manner that sends more request messages to the Olioboard.com servers in a given period of time than a human can reasonably produce in the same period by using a conventional on-line web browser. Notwithstanding the foregoing, Olioboard.com grants the operators of public search engines permission to use spiders to copy materials from the Website for the sole purpose of creating publicly available searchable indices of the materials, but not caches or archives of such materials. Olioboard.com reserves the right to revoke these exceptions either generally or in specific cases, in its sole discretion.

You agree not to collect or use any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") including without limitation account names, email addresses, or other User Submissions (as defined below), from the Website, nor use the communication systems provided by the Website for any commercial solicitation purposes, including without limitation to solicit, for commercial purposes, any users of the Website.

In 2010 we launched Olioboard in the hopes of giving people from all corners of the world the opportunity to create, share and shop room inspiration boards. We financed this new venture with the money we made from our web design business and took the plunge. It was exciting and terrifying all at once. 

What started as a simple online interior design platform morphed into not only a collection of 100,000’s of inspiring design boards, but also into an amazing and talented design community who shared their creations, competed in design challenges and encouraged and supported each other. 

This social sharing environment focused around interior design was precisely what made Olioboard unique; but ultimately this model proved to make it difficult to scale the business quickly enough to be fully self sustaining. 

Due to this we had to make the difficult decision to close down Olioboard. While it's sad to say goodbye, we're proud of what Olioboard was able to achieve and of the solid community that supported our efforts from the very beginning. 

If there’s one thing you learn when running a business it’s that when things don’t necessarily turn out the way you want, you never give up. You simply take time to rethink your options and pivot until you find a direction that does work. 

Thanks to Olioboard we found that new direction. 

* * *

By this time you have likely heard of, or seen the ads on Olioboard for our new professional design platform called [DesignFiles.](https://designfiles.co/r/olioboard?utm_source=olioboard&utm_campaign=olio_close)

Over the last year DesignFiles has been extremely well received in the design community and has quickly become one of the fastest growing online interior design platforms on the market. To date, DesignFiles provides thousands of designers, decorators and stagers with powerful interior design tools to streamline their workflow and captivate their clients. 

I’m happy to say we’ve built in all the best parts of Olioboard, newly enhanced and with the latest technology. 

If you are curious about how DesignFiles works, you can [watch it in action here.](https://designfiles.co/r/olioboard?utm_source=olioboard&utm_campaign=olio_close#video__how-df-works)

If you want to see what other designers are saying, here are the  [ratings and reviews.](https://www.capterra.com/p/179202/DesignFiles/)

* * *

I would highly recommend signing up for a [free account to test it out](https://designfiles.co/r/olioboard?utm_source=olioboard&utm_campaign=olio_close). I know that switching to a new platform can be daunting but I guarantee you will love the new enhancements and features. 

To make your transition an easy one we are happy to provide the following: 

**DesignFiles free trials + one-one demos:** Get everything that Olioboard had to offer plus a number of new features that will cut hours out of your workflow. 

**Product library transfer:** Any member who signs up for a paid account on DesignFiles will have their Olioboard product library transferred over to their new DesignFiles account. 

**63% off your first 3 months:** If you decide you like what you see you can use promo code DF63 to get 63% off your first 3 months of the Professional Plan. 

**5 star customer service:** Phone calls, live chat, emails and one-on-one demos. We’re here to make sure you have absolutely everything you need when you need it. 

[Try DesignFiles For Free](https://designfiles.co/r/olioboard?utm_source=olioboard&utm_campaign=olio_close) No credit card required for trial.

* * *

We’re taking steps immediately to ensure a smooth wind-down of Olioboard and to ensure that everyone has enough time to save their content or transition to DesignFiles. You’ll have until Dec 10th to download any images of your Olioboards for safe keeping. 

On November 15th we’ll be disabling account creation on Olioboard. 

On December 10th, we will officially shut down Olioboard and say a final goodbye to the members who helped make this dream a reality. It’s been an amazing ride. 

* * *

I’d like to take this opportunity to offer my deepest thanks to the Olioboard team both past and present, whose creativity, innovative thinking and dedication helped us build an online platform for 100,000’s of people from all from around the world to experiment and express their creativity through design. 

And of course to all our members: the ones who have been with us since the beginning, and the newly joined; the design enthusiasts and the design professionals, our biggest supporters and those who pushed us to excel further; and to all the friends we made along the way. 

Thank you all. 

Sheilah & the Olioboard team 

If you have any questions or concerns about these details, please don’t hesitate to email me at [sheilah@olioboard.com](mailto:sheilah@olioboard.com).
